There's one with no name on it.
c002
No name at all?
c003
Just the address. Handwritten.
c004
Then it's mine.
c005
How is it yours?
c006
I'm expecting something.
c007
You're always expecting something.
c008
Give it here.
c009
Not until we know.
c010
-Know what?
-Whose it is. Obviously.
c011
[unknown voice] Don't open that.
c012
Who was that?
c013
I thought we were alone.
c014
[unknown voice] I mean it. Put it down.
c015
-It's not yours.
-We weren't going to.
c016
[glass shatters]
c017
What was that?
c018
Not me.
c019
That was the jug. Sorry.
c020
Amara. When did you get in?
c021
Ten minutes ago. You two were busy.
c022
Is this yours?
c023
It is.
c024
What is it?
c025
I'll tell you when I've opened it.
c026
So open it.
c027
Not with you two watching.
c028
It's definitely hers, then.
c029
It was never yours.
c030
It could have been.
c031
Sweep up the jug.